[{"question": " hey, what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i found a note on my door, &quot;come to monica&#146;s quick, bring champagne and a three musketeers bar.&quot;", "answer": "  yeah i&#146;ll take that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what&#146;s up?", "answer": " monica and i are engaged.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " oh my god.  congratulations.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " yeah, she&#146;s been out there for twenty minutes, i&#146;m surprised you didn&#146;t hear her on the way over.", "answer": " oh, i thought it was just a kid yelling, &quot;i&#146;m gay! i&#146;m gay!&quot; can i bring her in?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " okay! wait-wait-wait! shhh!  okay, umm, i just wanna say that&#133;i love you guys so-so much and-and thank you for being here on my special night.  our special night. i mean it just wouldn&#146;t be my&#151;our-our night, if you all weren&#146;t here to celebrate with me&#151;us&#151;damnit!", "answer": " it&#146;s okay, i want this to be your night too.  to monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " awww, come on&#151;wait&#151;stop it. okay, to monica.", "answer": " to monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " so have you decided on a band for the wedding? because, y&#146;know, i&#146;m kinda musical.", "answer": " yeah pheebs, honey, she just got engaged a couple of hours ago. i doubt she&#146;s even had time to&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " well speaking of chiming in, remember the time you burned down my apartment?", "answer": "  yeah, you&#146;re on your own.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " but i-i-i can&#146;t stay too long, i gotta get up early for a commercial audition tomorrow and i gotta look good. i&#146;m supposed to be playing a 19-year-old.  what?", "answer": " so when you said, &quot;get up early,&quot; did you mean 1986?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " okay everybody, let&#146;s go! let&#146;s go!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  hey, is uh the rest of my candy bar around here?", "answer": " oh honey no, you ate it all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " know what i mean?", "answer": " yeah, but i don&#146;t think we have time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " there&#146;s gonna be a wedding. you&#146;re gonna be the bride. two hundred people are going to be looking at you in a clean white dress.", "answer": "  let&#146;s do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  chandler! it happens to lots of guys! you-you-you were probably tired, you had a lot of champagne, don&#146;t worry about it!", "answer": "  i&#146;m not worried, i&#146;m uh, i&#146;m fascinated. y&#146;know it&#146;s like uh, biology! which is funny because in high school i uh, i-i failed biology and tonight biology failed me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " check it out. okay, i can play this when the guests are coming in. okay.  &quot;first time i met chandler, i thought he was gay. but here i am singing on his wedding day!&quot;", "answer": " phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " sure, you guys don&#146;t have this problem, you&#146;re made of wood.  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " you look great!", "answer": "  oh, thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " you okay over there?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, y&#146;know? i feel a little umm&#133; no, y&#146;know what? nevermind, i&#146;m gonna be fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " wow! happy monica&#146;s night!", "answer": " well thank you, you too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " hey, do you believe this? do you believe they are actually getting married?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " well sure. but i get married all the time so&#133;", "answer": " ohh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " you okay?", "answer": " yeah, i guess. i-i&#133; i mean, do-do you think we&#146;re ever gonna have that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " you mean, we&#151;you and me?", "answer": " oh no-no-no-no-no, no, no! we, you with someone and me with someone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh good, you scared me for a minute.", "answer": " shake it off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " i mean&#151;no, it&#146;s just &#145;cause, it&#146;s just &#146;cause you and i were like a nightmare.  no, but there was some good times.", "answer": " no, absolutely. y&#146;know like it was umm&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " surely you can think of something good.", "answer": " yeah, just give me a minute!  oh well, yes, i can think of one good thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " well you uh, you were always really good at the uh, at the uh the stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yeah? i was good at the stuff huh?", "answer": " uh-hmm, uh-hmm, yeah, yeah, i really liked your hands.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " my hands?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  way to go guys. y&#146;know, you-you were really good at the stuff too.", "answer": " oh, i know. hey, y&#146;know what we never did?  oh no, not that.  we uh, we never had bonus night!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " a what?", "answer": " y&#146;know, bonus night. y&#146;know, when two people break up but they get back together for just one night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " one night, just-just sex. no strings attached?", "answer": " yeah-yeah, we never had that,", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " &#145;sup? &#145;sup dude?", "answer": "  take whatever you want, just please don&#146;t hurt me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " so you&#146;re playing a little playstation, huh? that&#146;s whack! playstation is whack! &#145;sup with the whack playstation, &#145;sup?! huh? come on, am i 19 or what?!", "answer": " yes, on a scale from 1 to 10, 10 being the dumbest a person can look, you are definitely 19.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " come on man, really how old?!", "answer": " young! you&#146;re a man-child okay?! now go get changed because everybody&#146;s ready and please, oh please, keep my underwear!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " joe?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " uhh, you&#146;ve had a lot of sex right?", "answer": " when? today? some, not a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " well, it&#146;s just the reason that i&#146;m asking is because i kind of eh, uh, i was unable to&#151;i mean i really wanted too, but i couldn&#146;t&#133;. there huh&#151;hmm, there-there was an incident.", "answer": " don&#146;t worry about that man, that happens.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " it&#146;s happened to you?", "answer": " yeah! once.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " well, what&#146;d you do?", "answer": " i did it anyway.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " phoebe! come on! let&#146;s go!  come on!  why aren&#146;t you dressed yet?!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, but i just wrote the best dance song for your wedding. check this out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  no, phoebe, i&#146;ll tell you what, if you get ready now i&#146;ll let you play it at the wedding.", "answer": " really?! oh that&#146;s so exciting! thank you! thanks mon! oh but mon, if you touch my guitar again i&#146;ll have to pound on you for a little bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " fair enough, now go get ready!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " okay, monica. mon, uh what-what you just saw&#133;", "answer": "  can i ask you just a little question, huh? why tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " see, i&#146;ve been waiting my whole life to be engaged, and unlike some people i&#146;m only planning on doing this once. so, uh y&#146;know, maybe this is selfish and i&#146;m sorry about it, but i was kinda hoping tonight could just be about that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " oh honey, but it is just about&#133;", "answer": " it is! it is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " no it&#146;s not! no! no! now it&#146;s about you and ross getting back together!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " see yeah umm, you kinda stole my thunder!", "answer": " okay! ho-ho! we did not steal your thunder because we are not getting back together!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " yeah. no. and you know what? nobody even saw!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " that&#146;s true.", "answer": " honey i swear it we just kissed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " you guys kissed!!!!! what does this mean?!! are you, are you getting back together?! can i sing at your wedding?", "answer": " thunder being stolen!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " okay come on phoebe, it&#146;s nothing! monica, come on!", "answer": " look let&#146;s not make a big deal out of this! it was a one time thing. it doesn&#146;t even matter!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " oh my god! i cannot believe you guys are talking about this! the problems in the bedroom are between the man and the woman!!! all right?!! now chandler is doing the best he can!!", "answer": "  i don&#146;t think that&#146;s what they were talking about joe!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " you guys kissed! oh my&#151;this is huge!", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh no!", "answer": " no-no, it&#146;s really not huge.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " and; people thinking it&#146;s huge has led monica to believe that we are stealing her thunder.  which we are not!", "answer": " well, we&#146;re still talking about it, aren&#146;t we?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " well yeah, that and chandler&#146;s problem.", "answer": " monica-monica-monica-monica, listen-listen, listen, listen, would-would it make you feel better if we all stop talking about ross and rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " yes that would be lovely.", "answer": " you got it. okay. now, i can pass for 19 right?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " yes, you can pass for 19.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " seriously?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " seriously? seriously, no! you can play your own age which is 31!", "answer": "  i&#146;m 30!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " joey, you are not! you&#146;re 31.", "answer": "  aww crap!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay, so the plaza! okay, we&#146;ll get us some mai thai&#146;s,  maybe no more for you though.", "answer": " y&#146;know what? i-i think that umm, i don&#146;t feel like going to the plaza.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " why?!", "answer": " honey, monica, this is ridiculous! look&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  yeah?  okay, i think i&#146;ll play it at the wedding.", "answer": " yeah! well, i think we&#146;ll see if they actually let you play. huh? i mean they tell you anything you want to hear like-like, &quot;you look 19,&quot; and then they just take it away like-like, &quot;no you don&#146;t.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well, i don&#146;t think monica is gonna take this away.", "answer": " wouldn&#146;t she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " would she?", "answer": " would she?  you ate my candy bar!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey, i just realized we kinda let some stuff up in the air&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " what do you think monica mean when she said she didn&#146;t want to talk, especially with me? i mean, why not especially you and me? we were both out there kissing.", "answer": " still thinking about it huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " come on! serious-ser-ser-seriously, what did she mean by that?  especially you!", "answer": "  oh, who cares?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i care!", "answer": "  and so do i.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " y&#146;know what, i-i have to go talk to her, would you let me just get changed?", "answer": " okay. sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " am i going to let you watch me undress?", "answer": "  no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe her, y&#146;know it&#146;s just&#151;it&#146;s so typical.", "answer": " now monica, i know you&#146;re upset, but don&#146;t forget. there is going to be a wedding, you are going to throw the bouquet, and then there&#146;s going to be a honeymoon, maybe in paris.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " paris?", "answer": " we will take a moonlit walk on the rue de la .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " keep talking.", "answer": " then we will sprinkle rose pedals on the bed and make love. not just because it&#146;s romantic, but because i can!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  bonjour, monsieur.", "answer": " okay, don&#146;t say anything, you might scare it away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " it&#146;s paris, who knows we&#146;re here!", "answer": "  hi pheebs, what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay, you said i could sing at your wedding so, i&#146;m just gonna need a small deposit.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " y&#146;know, just some good faith money to hold the date.", "answer": " pheebs, we&#146;re not giving you a deposit for our wedding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " they break your heart, don&#146;t they?", "answer": " y&#146;know, i don&#146;t really their permission.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " yeah! if you wanna sing at their wedding, well you sing at their wedding!", "answer": " yeah! and if you wanna look 19, then you&#133; you gotta do something about your eyes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " what?! what&#146;s wrong with my eyes.", "answer": " they give you away! there&#146;s just-there&#146;s just too much wisdom in there.  just put some tea bags on there for like 15 minutes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " and that&#146;ll get rid of my wisdom?", "answer": " maybe just 10 minutes for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " monica, what did you mean before when you said you didn&#146;t want to talk to anyone, especially me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " what a great apology!  and you accept! okay, bye-bye!", "answer": " no-no, seriously-seriously, what was the especially me part about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " well, let&#146;s just say it&#146;s not the first time you&#146;ve stolen my thunder.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " monica, what are you talking about?", "answer": " my sweet sixteen! remember, you went to third base with my cousin charlie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  ahh, third base.", "answer": " it&#146;s all everybody at the party could talk about!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " monica, y&#146;know what? the only reason i did that was because your party was so boring!", "answer": "  we had a characturist!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh!!", "answer": "  &quot;whenever i get married, guess who won&#146;t get to sing? somebody named geller! and somebody else named bing!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " monica, your sweet sixteen was like a million years ago.", "answer": " and yet, here we are doing it again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " ugh, monica i don&#146;t want to steal your stupid thunder!", "answer": " oh please! why else would you have made out with ross?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " all right, easy mimey, the moment has passed, it ain&#146;t gonna happen!", "answer": " i just thought it would be nice if i could have just this one night!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i swear, i never wanted any part of your night!", "answer": " oh, is that why you did it the secret hallway where nobody ever goes?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " uh, rachel, i&#146;ve been thinking. i don&#146;t think us getting together tonight is such a good idea. i&#146;m calling it off.", "answer": "  why to save your dignity my man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  monica, why? why would i ever want to take away from your night?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know! i don&#146;t&#151;maybe you&#146;re feeling a little resentful. maybe ah, maybe you thought you&#146;d get married first! maybe you can&#146;t stand the fact that your formally fat friend is getting married before you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  i can&#146;t believe you&#146;re gonna have sex on my engagement night!!", "answer": " well, somebody should.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " look uh, if we&#146;re gonna do this&#133;", "answer": " we&#146;re not gonna do this, all right? she&#146;s just gonna think that we&#146;re doin&#146; it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " who is it?", "answer": "  it&#146;s monica, open up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " oww!", "answer": " yeah, you like that baby?  may we help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " i just wanted to say that i hope you do have sex tonight and i hope that you guys get back together, but i must warn you, the night that you announce your engagement i&#146;m going to announce that i&#146;m pregnant!", "answer": " how is that ever going to happen?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " all right monica, do you want to know why i was with ross tonight?!", "answer": " i know why!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " no you don&#146;t know why!", "answer": " okay! why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " because! because i was sad.", "answer": " what do you mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t care, she slept with me.", "answer": " anyway sweetie, i am, i&#146;m so sorry i ruined your night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": "  well, i&#146;m going to take off.  congratulations man.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": "  and uh, rachel.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": "  &quot;we thought phoebe would leave, but she just stayed and stayed. that&#146;s right, i&#146;m here all night, and chandler will never get l&#133;&quot;", "answer": "  hey! here&#146;s a dollar, consider it a deposit. please sing at our wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " oh thank you.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}]